>> Jem: 为何完整堆栈?
&gt;&gt; Jem: And why full stack?
我知道，我确实在对什么是完整的栈进行了骚扰，并且在这个定义上。
I know, I'm really harping on what is
full stack, and going on this definition.
因为如果你说你是个完整的工程师
Because again,
if you say you're a full stack engineer,
有些人是这样的人不是真实的
there are people that are like,
that's not a real thing.
当我听到满满的时候，或者我得到很多招聘者，
And when I hear full stack, or
I get a lot of recruiters reach out and
说我需要一个完整的堆工程师
say, hey, I need a full stack engineer.
我想他们想要一个黑客[ LAUGH]
What I think is they want a hacker,
[LAUGH] but
他们不知道他们需要什么
they don't know what they need.
所以他们说我想要一个擅长什么的人因为我们会知道
So they say, I want someone who's good at
everything because we'll figure out what
你需要的时候才需要
you need when you get here.
如果你想去的话也可以
That's okay too if that's
kind of where you wanna go.
我开始做满堆的
I started doing full stack.
我开始在 PHP 工作， PHP 可以考虑一个通用的
I started working in PHP, which PHP
you can consider one of the universal
您可以在后端中编码的语言，您可以在前端进行编码。
languages that you can code in
the backend, you can code in the frontend.
其实不是不好的语言。
It's actually not a bad language.
它有很多的 flack ，但我认为是低估了。
It gets a lot of flack,
but underrated I think.
但你在职业生涯的某个时候就满身了
But you went full stack because
at some point in your career,
你会看到这些东西的
you're gonna see all these things.
我们今天来的所有概念如果你要做 10年的工程师
All the concepts we come over today,
if you're gonna be an engineer for 10, 15,
二十，不管你想做工程师多久，都能看到这些东西。
20, however long you wanna be an engineer,
you're gonna see all these things.
我想让你熟悉他们
And I want you to be familiar with them.
这就是它的真实情况。
And that's really what it's about.
老实说我现在就告诉你这只是我们之间的
And honestly, I'll tell you now,
and it's just between us and
互联网上有些陌生的陌生人，有很多 UI 工程师。
some random strangers on the Internet,
there's a lot of UI engineers.
UI 工程可能是一个很容易进入的领域
UI engineering is probably one
of the easy fields to get into,
因为您只需打开浏览器，就可以开始进行编码。
because you can just open up browser and
just start coding.
那就好
And that's good.
每个人都应该像个工程师
Everybody should think like an engineer.
不是每个人都是
Well, not everybody, but
大家都应该明白这个世界是如何运作的，这个技术是如何运作的。
everybody should understand how the world
works, how this technology works.
但如果你想区分自己理解完整的堆栈
But if you wanna differentiate yourself,
understanding full stack,
了解它是如何走到一起的，会使你成为一个更好的工程师。
understanding how it all comes together,
will make you the better engineer.
在世界上所有 UI 工程师中，即使你不做任何事情
Amongst all the UI engineers in the world,
even if you don't do any of the stuff ever
再一次知道你是个更好的工程师
again, just knowing makes
you a better engineer.
我可以这么说
That much I can say that.
这就是为什么我喜欢这样做，因为它很有帮助。
And that's why I like to do this course,
because it's just so helpful.
这对我的事业很有帮助，因为你永远不知道自己要做什么。
It's been so helpful in my career because
you never know what you have to do.
实际上， >> Jem: 在 Netflix 我以前
In fact,
&gt;&gt; Jem: At Netflix I used to,
好吧，我还是做，但是我以前是个 IC ，所以
well, I still do, but
I used to be an IC, so
是主队的个人投稿人
that's individual contributor
on the frontend team.
我在非会员那边工作
I worked on the non-member side.
所以如果你去 netflix.com 或者在电视上，
So if you go to netflix.com or
on the TV, any of that stuff,
那是我工作的领域
that's the domain I worked in.
所以如果你不登录，那就是我的团队。
So if you're not logged in,
that's my team.
但我做的就是做了很多 A/B 测试
But what I did was I
built a lot of A/B tests.
所以我们不断地测试事物。
So we test things constantly.
但现在我离开了
But now I moved away from that.
现在我在我们的一个核心小组工作。
Now I work on one of our core teams.
因此，它位于 UI 部分之间。
So that sits between the UI section.
它坐在一个平台层之间。
And it sits between kind
of the platform layer.
我在中间工作
I work in between there.
主要在节点上，就像这样。
So primarily on Node, things like that.
>> Jem: 上周我花了所有时间做了一个 [LAUGH] 数据库迁移，
&gt;&gt; Jem: I've spent all of last week
doing a [LAUGH] database migration,
因为我选择了 Redis 来建立一个服务现在我要搬去 MySQL了
because I chose Redis to build
a service and I'm now moving to MySQL.
我得把这些都挂了
And I've had to hook these all up.
负载均衡器有问题。
I had a problem with the load balancer.
某些安全许可权不正确。
Some of the security
permissions were incorrect.
我得帮你修好
I had to fix the caching.
让我说我不详细说明
Let me just say,
I won't go into details, but
我必须做很多事情需要我去了解到底发生了什么
I had to do a lot of things that required
me to understand exactly what's happening.
如果我说我只是个 UI 工程师那我就知道该怎么做了
And if I said, I'm just the UI engineer,
that's I'll know what to do,
我不会走很远的
I would not have gotten very far.
再次成为一个完整的工程师和工程师
So again, being a full stack engineer and
了解这些东西是非常有价值的
understanding these things
is incredibly valuable.
我不是说因为你坐在那儿看这个课程
And I'm not just saying that because
you're sitting there watching this course,
我这么说是因为我真的相信
I'm saying it because
I truly believe that.